isocket.com 2013-08-30

# isocket

##  Privacy Policy 

isocket values your privacy. We make every reasonable effort to protect and respect your personal and sensitive information. 

This document will describe how we handle your personal information on the isocket website. This Privacy Policy applies to isocket.com and other related websites where this policy appears in the footer of the page. 

By agreeing to the Terms of Service and using this site, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective on May 14, 2008. 

## Information Collected

You can enter isocket and browse sockets and our sites without giving out personal information. We collect your IP address and standard web log information, such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our website. 

If you sign up for an account, we ask you to input the following information: 

  * first and last name 
  * email address 
  * physical contact information 
  * password 

When you sign up for additional services or Buy/Sell advertising opportunities on isocket.com we ask you to provide the following information 

  * financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers; 
  * transactional information based on your activities on the sites (such as bidding, buying, selling, item and content you generate or that relates to your account); 
  * shipping, billing and other information you provide to purchase or ship materials; 
  * community discussions, chats, dispute resolution, correspondence through our sites, and correspondence sent to us; 
  * other information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information; 
  * information from other companies, such as demographic and traffic data; and 
  * other supplemental information from third parties (if you incur a debt to isocket or need to verify your information, we will generally conduct a credit check by obtaining additional information about you from a credit bureau, as permitted by law; or if the information you provide cannot be verified, we may ask you to send us additional information, such as your driver license, credit card statement, or a recent utility bill or other information confirming your address, or to answer additional questions online to help verify your information). 

## Additional Verification

There are times when the isocket team needs to verify your identity for your safety and the safety of other users. We may ask you to provide additional information we can use to verify your identity, address, organization, billing or invoicing information and managed risk. The following information may be asked of you to provide: 

  * date of birth 
  * social security number 
  * EIN number 

We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as credit bureaus and identity verification services. 

When you are using our Service, we collect information about your account transactions and we may collect information about your computer or other access device for fraud prevention purposes. 

Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store results when you respond to a survey. 

## Use of Cookies

When you access isocket.com, we, or third party companies we use to better understand how our website is used, may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. 

We use these cookies sent to browser to recognize you and if you visit multiple pages on our site during the same session we dont need keep asking you for your password on every page. Once you log out or close your browser, this cookie will expire and will no longer interact with isocket.com. 

We can also use longer-lasting cookies to display your e-mail address on our sign-in form, so that you don't need to retype the e-mail address each time you log in to your account. 

Cookies are optional and most browsers allow you to block cookies from certain sites. However, by blocking cookies from isocket.com, certain features and functions will not be able to be used. 

## Protect and Store Information

At isocket, your security is a primary concern. We use the lasted and most secure measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. 

All personal information is stored on our computers in the US, and we protect it by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable US federal and state regulations. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files, and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities. 

We also use SSL encrypted transmissions between your Web browser and our Web server for personal and financial information. This is designed to reduce the chance that someone on your network at work or at your Internet service provider may try to compromise your private information as it travels from your Web browser to our secure server. When transmitted data is encrypted you will see a security notice when you enter an encrypted page, and by the presence of an icon on your browser, either a key for Netscape or a lock for Microsoft Internet Explorer. The pages where you submit your account information, place a bid, and receive confirmation of a successful bid are all encrypted. In addition, your credit card information is encrypted within our database and access to such information is restricted. 

## Use of Information

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. We may use your personal information to: 

  * process transactions and send notices about your transactions 
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; 
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement; 
  * customize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website; 
  * send you targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; 
  * compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties. 

If isocket becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

## Sharing Information

To purchase or sell advertising opportunities, we need to share some of your personal information with the person or company that you are involved in a transaction with. Your contact information, date of sign-up, the number of transactions you have completed, and other information may be viewed by other users. 

We will never disclose your credit card number or bank account number to anyone you have entered in a transaction with, except with your express permission or if we are required to do so to comply with a subpoena or other legal process. 

We may share your personal information with: 

  * Other companies to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts, provide joint services and for other business purposes. However, these corporate affiliates will not use this information to market their services to you unless you have approved it. 
  * Service providers under contract who help with parts of our business operations; (fraud prevention, bill collection, marketing, technology services). Our contracts dictate that these service providers only use your information in connection with the services they perform for us and not for their own benefit. 
  * Financial institutions that we partner with to process payments and provide other services to you. 
  * Credit bureaus to report outstanding negative balance accounts, as allowed by law. 
  * Companies that we plan to merge with or to be acquired by. 
  * Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when 
    * we are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order or similar legal procedure 
    * we need to do so to comply with law 
    * we believe in good faith that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our User Agreement. 
  * Other third parties with your consent or direction to do so. 

isocket will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties in the normal course of doing business and only shares your personal information with third parties as described in this policy. 

## Settings

You can at any time control how we use your contact information to market our services to you in the notifications preferences under 

## My Account

You can review your personal information and make any necessary changes, at any time by logging in to your account and changing your preferences in the Profile page of the 

## Contact

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you can contact us by email: [support@isocket.com](mailto:support@isocket.com)

Or write to us at: 

      isocket  C/O Privacy
      270 East Ln.
      Suite #1
      Burlingame, CA 94010
